Hello friends, welcome to our
YouTube channel Bijli Hum. Are you also
facing any problem in downloading the Ayushman card like the latest session
expired and your payment bar is failing?
If you are facing this problem then you should
click on the right video. Friends,
in this video we will tell you the training
which will solve your problem.
So friends, those who are new to our channel,
quickly subscribe to the channel and
press the bell icon so that if any
requested video comes, you
can get a notification. So
friends, let's start the video. First of all,
we will come to Google Chrome and
after coming to Google Chrome, we will come to the mode to
space settings here.
After setting, what we have to do is click here.
As soon as we click on settings,
we have to click on these three dots visible here
and after that
click on About Chrome and here we
can see the playlist. Our version is 72
whose Google Chrome weight is 600.
It is getting updated here automatically. This is
local, this tweet is not going to be updated.
So what do we have to do for this friends, let's go
to the back and what will we do here, we will come
down to our search bar to stop the update
and here we will type Ranjodh,
after typing run friends we will click here
and after clicking here
we will find MS Config here and
after writing it we will replace it, after that
as we click it once and
type it here, here in front of us there is a
section called 'Channel', it will
definitely be open here but you do
not have to go to the channel, you have to CR
above the service, after the service comes on it
you have to search Google here,
then keep scrolling and find Google,
where is Google written, you will find
Google written here,
there will be two-three Google things,
we have to uncheck them all, here
you can see that you could not find all the
applications, it
is very difficult but
where we have two Google's, we have unchecked them, so
what will we do first,
you will find this a good way  Let us tell you that
Chakmak is in this way, how to do it,
when you say we will
get it in this way and it will be Hrithik, but you have to
remove the tick from it and
apply and ok the ticket that comes here,
after that if you want to register then you
can install it, otherwise you
can also do the withdrawal and then the old
update you have will be turned off and the Google
Chrome app which will not be updated,
let's go back to its check, we will do the
settings, click on the free line, after that
go to the about room,
we will check here,
what is our weight, it is 600, that checker updates
is written but it is not getting updated, so you
have to do this setting, after this you
download and use Google Chrome, you will be able to easily
download your Ayushman card and will be
able to print it easily, you will neither
see the option of main request, session expired nor payment again,
so let us live and show you by downloading a small card now  Yes, so
first of all we login here on Abhishek's
site on CBC,
so to login we will click here, we will be
on its main site,
click on the side like Ayushman Bharat PM
and after clicking, it will ask us to
enter CSC ID and password for Vishwas's side,
so here we enter our CID and
password, after
taking the CSC ID and password we
click on sign in, as soon as we
click on sign in, it will ask us to confirm
C idol-worship, we will do it from here,
after that we have to give our finger print
bell question here,
so let's take authentication,
see here, as you have seen now, it is not happening,
unless you do this it will
not update automatically, so we give authentication,
sign it, click on chart capture,
if we do it again the finger print will be
ready for recording and
what we will do by putting our finger print here, we will
login  If we take it, then
bring to front has been installed here,
we have successfully logged in, so
here we go to the approved section on the home page of our Ayushman Bharat today
and see it in the home set,
this network was done in the century, now we had
made a car in the state, so
we enter the date here,
after entering for some time, we enter this month 2020
here, after that we will submit
and we got an attack here,
I will click on request confirm print,
as if clicking on confirm print,
it will take us to the site of our CSC wallet
and here it will ask us to enter the password,
we enter the password here, after that
click on validate, after clicking on
validate, friends,
we will enter the pin here, after entering it we will click on click and as soon as we
repair it, here our tree
goes to school, friends, you can take it and you are
not able to see any of it in the day,
neither the destruction of the meeting waste
nor the expiry of the page  Let's download it,
click on card download,
this is our work, the download has
started,
I was using the internet, then we
click on download,
come on the download card,
until your card is downloaded,
you will not have to make any
payment again and our account which is
downloaded, we open it by clicking on it, so
this work is ours, it was in the name of more
and this Gujhiya is also the latest, see
Modi ji's photo is coming here,
of the arrested minister, which is absolutely
latest and new for you and you can also see the update
that it is Katju bread, it was
generated on 5th April, so I hope you
liked the video, if you liked it then do
n't forget to like, share and subscribe to the channel
friends